<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="79">
    <author>Farmsim Tim (timmeey86)</author>
    <version>1.0.2.1</version>
    <title>
        <en>Tree Value Info</en>
        <de>Baumpreis Info</de>
    </title>
    
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[This mod calculates information for trees and pieces of wood and displays them in the info box:

- The volume of the tree or piece of wood in liters
- The current value, which is the amount of money you would get if you sold the tree in its current form
- A recommendation for a cut if splitting the piece of wood would result in more total money
- The amount of liters you would get when processing the tree with a wood chipper
- The amount of money you would get if you sold the wood chips right now
- An estimation of money you would get if you sold the wood chips at best price (sometimes you can get more than that, due to randonmness)

Note that the value of a piece of wood depends on these three factors (default behavior for FS22):
- The shape (best value if straight)
- The number of side branches still attached (best value if fully delimbed)
- The length (best value if between 6m and 11m)

It is recommended to use the lumberjack or the measure mod in order to find the desired cut position.

Changelog:
Version 1.0.2.0:
- Info Box is now displayed whenever the ring around a piece of wood is visible (caused by an equipped chainsaw)
- Removed cut length recommendation (too inaccurate) and added quality

Version 1.0.1.0:
- Added wood chip info
]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[Diese Mod berechnet den aktuellen Preis für einen Baum oder ein Stück Holz und zeigt diese Informationen an.

Der "Aktuelle Wert" ist der Preis, den man bekommen würde, wenn man den Baum oder das Stück Holz in seiner aktuellen Form verkauft.

Beachtet, dass der Wert von Holz von diesen drei Faktoren abhängt (Standardverhalten von FS22):
- Die Form (Am wertvollsten, wenn gerade)
- Die Anzahl an Zweigen, die noch vorhanden sind (Am wertvollsten, wenn vollständig entastet)
- Die Länge (Am wertvollsten zwischen 6m und 11m)

Die Mod gibt daher Vorschläge für den besten Schnitt, wenn anwendbar.

Es wird empfohlen, die Holzfäller Mod oder die Maßband Mod zu verwenden, um die gewünschte Stelle für den Schnitt zu finden.

Changelog:
Version 1.0.2.0:
- Info Box wird nun immer angezeigt, solange ein Ring um ein Stück Holz sichtbar ist (wenn man eine Kettensäge benutzt)
- Vorschlag zur optimalen Schnittlänge entfernt (zu ungenau) und Qualitäts-Wert hinzugefügt
Version 1.0.1.0:
- Informationen für Hackschnitzel hinzugefügt
]]></de>
    </description>
    
    <multiplayer supported="true" />

    <iconFilename>icon_TreeValueInfo.dds</iconFilename>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/WoodPriceCalculation.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/TreeValueInfo.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <l10n filenamePrefix="i18n/locale" />
</modDesc>